Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- H
  - Heynes, Barbara, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Hibschman, Nelson, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Hickey, Joseph, 1929-1930 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Hicks, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Hiddal, Freda T., 1953 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Hidy, Ralph, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Higginbotham, Hal, 1977, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Hilferty, Susan, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Hill, Anita, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Hill, Arthur E., 1932, 1936-1937 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Hill, Bill, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Mary, undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Hill, Mozel, undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Hilliard, Thomas, circa 1933 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Hillman, Lucille, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Hinick, Claus F., undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Hindle, Brooke, 1962, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Hine, Eve, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Hinkhouse, undated (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Hirsch, Gloria B., 1961 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Hirsch, Joan, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Hirsch, Stuart M., 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Hirschfield, Henry I., 1963 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Hirschhorn, Herbert, undated (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Hirshman, Elizabeth, undated (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Hitchcock, Charlotte, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Hite, Shere, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Hittner, Judge David, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Hliddal, F., undated (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Ho, Thomas, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Hochberg, Julian, undated (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Hockney, David, 1992
    - Photographs (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Hodes, Stuart, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Hodges, Charles, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Hodges, Luther, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Hoe, A.G., undated (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Hoexter, Joan, 1964, 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Hoffman, Abbie, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Hoffman, Doris S., undated (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Hoffman, Dustin, undated (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Hoffman, Grace Fletcher, undated (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Hoffman, Philip Seymour, undated (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Hoffman, Theodore, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Hofstatler, Ellen, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Hogedon, Anne, circa 1983 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Hogg, Robert, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - Hoire, Tetsuya, undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Holbert, Hayward, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - Hold, Cervantes, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - Holden, Frederick Clark, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Holden, Randy, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Holder, Barbara, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Holland, Daniel M., undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Hollander, Edward, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Hollander, Lawrence J., 1966 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Hollings, Ernest, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Hollinshead, Merrill T., 1960 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Holliwell, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Holly, Frank, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Holman, Wayne J., 1956, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Holmes, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Holmes, H. Frederick, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell Jr., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Holmes, Stephen, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Holt, L. Emmett, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Holt, Robert R., 1964, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Holton, Gerald, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Holzknecht, Karl, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Holtzman, Liz, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Holzman, Robert S., undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Holzman, Samuel, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Hood, Ann, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1961-1984 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Hoopingarner, Newman, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Hoost, Allen John, undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Hooten, Denise, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Hoover, David F., undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1949 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Hopf, Hans E., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Hopf, Harry A., undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Hopkins, Hoyt S., 1942 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Hopkins, Treadwell H., 1960 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Hoppock, Robert, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Hopt, Klaus, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Horman, undated (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Hormel, H. Dudley, undated (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Hornstein, Benjamin S., undated (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Hornstein, George, 1963-1977 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Hornstein, George and Lillian, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Hornstein, Jordan, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Hornstein, Lillian H., 1964, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Horowitz, Alfred H., undated (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Horowitz, Ann, undated (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Horowitz, Helen, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Horsen, Norman, undated (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Horwitz, Jay, undated (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Hosack, David, undated (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Hosay, Philip, undated (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Hotchkiss, George B., 1950 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Houghton, Charles E., undated (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Houghton, Dale, 1942, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Houghton, William A., undated (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Houk, Dale W., 1963 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Houlahan, James, undated (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Houle, Cyril Orvin, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Houlihan, Dennis, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Hovner, Anthony, undated (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Howard, undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Howard, George S., undated (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Howard, James, undated (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Howard, Lawrence, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Howell, Paul, undated (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Howell, Robert, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Howley, Frank, 1952, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - Hoy, Pat C., undated (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Hoydisdt, Walter G., 1975 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Hrushovski, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Hsu, T.C., undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Huang, Alice, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Hubin, Dr. Dorothea, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Huddlestan, John, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Hug, Elsie, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Huggins, Patrick, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1908 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Hughes, Diane, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Hughes, Eileen, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Hughes, Graham, 1973, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Hughes, Richard E., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Hugret, Joseph "Sugar", circa 1933 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Hull, George H., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Hulme, Harold, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Hume, Donald, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Hunegs, Craig, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Hungerfeld, E. Arthur, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Hunkins, Maurel, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Hunt, Clinton Nottage, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Hunt, Randy, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Hunt, Richard, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Hunter, Nam, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Huntington, Henry Edwards, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Huntley, Chet, undated (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Harley, Beatrice J., 1963 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Hurley, Patricia M., undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Hurley, Ros T., undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Hurme, Risto, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Hurt, Mary Beth, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Hurvitz, undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Hurwitz, Leo, undated (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Huskes, Howard, undated (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Hussein, King of Jordan, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Hutkins, Steve, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Hutton, Ron, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1965, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Hyde, W. Lewis, 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Hyman, Irving, circa 1938 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Hyman, Isabelle, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Hyman, Milton, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 41)
- I
  - Archbishop Iakovos, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Ibi, Keiko, undated (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Ibos, Margaret, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Ice-T, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Idol, Billy, undated (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Ignation, Archie, undated (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Iizuka, Leo, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Illuzi, John, undated (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Imarata, Rudolph, 1965, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Imperatore, Arthur, undated (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Imperatore, Payne, undated (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - Imus, Don, undated (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Professor Ing, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Ingberg, Holger, undated (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Ingersoll, William H., undated (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Inglehart, Robert L., undated (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Ingram, William, undated (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - Injoom, Kim, undated (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Insanally, S.R., undated (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - Ionescu, Eugène, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Ippolito, Michael, undated (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - Ippolito, Raymond, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - Irvin, Sam, undated (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - Lord Irvine, undated (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Irving, David, undated (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Irwin, Ray, undated (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - Irwin, William P., undated (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - Isaacs, Abram S., 1938 (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Isaacson, Eugene, undated (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - Ishar, Iqbal, undated (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Israel, Edward, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Issacharoff, Sam, undated (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - Istok, Edward, circa 1935 (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Ivey, John E., Jr., undated (Box 54, Folder 71)
- J
  - Jablow, Paul, undated (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Jackerman, Bill, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - Jackson, Andrew, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Fred, 1965, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Holmes C., undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, Raymond S., 1958 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, Samuel Macauley, 1898, 1903 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Susan, undated (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Jacobs, James B., 1983-1986
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Jacobson, Richard A., undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Jacoby, Jack, 1982-1984 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Jacobziner, Harold, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Jaffa, Herbert C., 1963 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Jaffe, Jo, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Jaffe, Leo, 1979-1986 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Jaggart, John Y., undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Jahn, George P., undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Jahoda, Marie, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Jama, Abdula, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - James, Debra, 1999
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - James, Dorothea Draper, undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - James, Eric, undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - James, Henry, 1967
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - James, Philip, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - James, Robert C., undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - James, Thomas, undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - James, William III, undated
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Janeway, E.G., undated (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Janis, J. Harold, undated (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Janoff, Ronald, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Janson, Horst, 1961-1974 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Jaques, David R., undated
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Jarke, Matthias, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Jarmusch, Jim, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Jarvick, Robert K., undated (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Jarvis, J. Pitts, Jr., 1956 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Jarvis, N. Leonard, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Jasper, Jim, undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Jasso, Guillermina, undated (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Javits, Jacob, 1959-1968 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Jay, Alice and Henry, undated (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Jefferson, Margot, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Jenkins, Carol, undated (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Jenkins, Adelbert, 1982
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Jenkins, Len, undated (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Jenkins, Robert B., 1940 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Jenks, Ann, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Jenness, Linda, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Jenrette, Richard H., 1976 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Jensen, Bill, undated (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Jensen, Grady E., 1956 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Jensen, Tim, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Jernow, Allison Liu, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Jerome, Fred, undated (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Jeske, Robert, undated (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Jessau, Alain, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Jiminey, Rafael, undated (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Jobling, Pat, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Joffre, Jean Jaques, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - John, Fritz, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - John, Hilda, 1984-1989 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - John, Kose, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Pope John Paul II, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Arnold W., undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Carmen D., undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Don, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Donald, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, E.A., 1857-1938 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Evelyne, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Herbert, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, James Weldon, 1871-1938 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Janette, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Joseph F., 1903-1969 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Jotham, 1960
    - Photographs (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Johnson, Laglenda, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Malcolm C., 1973, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Mark H., undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, Patrice, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Paula, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Johnson, Phillip, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Phillip -- Chemistry, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Robert, undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Johnson, Samuel, circa 1941 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, Theodore, undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Johnson, Thomas A., undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Johnston, Donald, undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Johnston, Gerald C., undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Johnston, John, 1949
    - Photographs (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Johnston, John, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Johnston, John Taylor, 1930, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Johnston, Kristin, undated (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Johnston, Sean, undated (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Jolly, Clifford, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Jones, Astor, undated (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Jones, Colin, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Jones, H. Edward, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Jones, James Earl, undated (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Jones, Jesse Holman, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Jones, Joseph, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Jones, Joy, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Jones, Philip, 1980, 1982
    - Photographs (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Thatcher, undated (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Jones, Theodore F., 1906-1951 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Jones, Vincent L., undated (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Jones, William D., 1970 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Jong, Erica, undated (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Jonghandle, undated (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Joran, Alvin, undated (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Jordan, Barbara, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Jordan, Henry P., undated (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Jordan, Steve, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - Jordan, William Marsh, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 53)
  - Josephson, Ben, undated (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Jovans, Bernard, undated (Box 56, Folder 54)
  - Jowitt, Deborah, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 55)
  - Joyce, James, undated (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Joynt, John, circa 1934 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Judd, Orrin R., undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Judt, Tony, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Julian, Anthony, undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Julian, Rodney, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Jung, Nawab, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Juran, Joseph M., undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Jurow, Irving H., 1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Jussenrand, Jules, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Juul, Tom, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- K
  - Kacen, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Kaelber, Walter, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Kagey, Rudolf, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Kaham, Marcel, 2005
    - Photographs (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Kahane, Meir, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Kahn, Edmund, undated (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Kahn, Robert, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Kahn, Robert, undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Kahn, Roger, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Kaifu, Toshiki, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Kaim, James M., 2000 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Kalamotousakis, George, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Kalay, Avner, undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Kalb, Milton, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Kalb, Richard J., undated (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Kalban, Steve, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Kalinkowitz, Bernard, 1961, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Kalish, Andy, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Kallberg, Jarl, undated (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Kallek, Delores, undated (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Kallenbach, Neville, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Kallman, Harmut, 1958-1968 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Kalman, Tibor, undated (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Kalodner, Howard I., 1976 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Kalton, Marc, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Kamanyi, Margit, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Kambysellis, Michael, undated (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Kames, Harry, circa 1938 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Kamm, Frances Myrna, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Kammerer, John Joseph, undated (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Kammorowski, Mark, undated (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Kampelman, Max M., 1982-1988
    - Photographs (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Kanbar, Maurice, undated (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Kane, David S., 1962-1965 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Kane, Thomas J., 1979 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Kang, Younghill, undated (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Kann, undated (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Kann, Kotan, undated (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Kantor, Jay, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Kaplan, Bruce, 1963, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Kaplan, Carline, undated (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Kaplan, Flora, 1979
    - Photographs (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Kaplan, Ira, undated (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Kaplan, Ken, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Kaplan, Marilyn, undated (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - Kaplan, Mordecai, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - Kaplan, Ralph, undated (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - Kaplan, Rita and Stanley H., 1983-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Kaplan, Steve, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Kaplan, William B., 1986 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Kapleen, Helene, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Karant, Joe, circa 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Karlan, Pamela, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Karlen, Delmar, 1952-1962 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Karlin, Margaret Fuller, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Karlinsky, Stewart, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Karmel, Roberta S., undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Karol, John, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Karp, A., undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Karras, Sehnap, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Kars, Elinor, 1957-1958 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Karshetz, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Kasa, Pamela, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Kasdorf, Julia, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Kastner, Elwood C., 1941 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Katfer, William, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Kathis, Ken, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Katsh, Abraham I., 1944-1976 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Katz, Barry, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Katz, Benjamin, undated (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Katz, Dan, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Katz, Kenneth, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Katzell, Raymond, 1963-1968 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Katzman, Ken, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Kaufman, Edward G., 1966 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Kaufman, Henry, 1958-1992 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Kaufman, Howard, circa 1937 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Kaufman, Irving, undated (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Kaufman, Lloyd, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Kaufman, Sandy, undated (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Kaufman, Victor A., undated (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Kaufman, William, circa 1944-1945 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Kavanagh, Frank Edge, 1903 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Kavanagh, John, undated (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Kavanaugh, E., 1946 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Kavanaugh, Thomas C., 1952 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Kavesh, Robert A., 1967-1983 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Kawamura, Shigekuni, undated (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Kaye, Danny, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Kaye, Ira S., 1941-1973 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Kaye, Judith Smith, 1991-1995 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Kaynard, Samuel M., undated (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Kazemi, Farhad, undated (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Kean, Thomas, undated (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Keane, Helen, 1952, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Kearing, Samuel J., undated (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Kearny, Lynn, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Kearse, Lee Andrew, Jr., 1969 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Keck, Sheldon, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Keda, Ken, undated (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Keely, Mary, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - Keenan, Michael, circa 1990-1999 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - Keeton, Pat, undated (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - Keil, Frank, undated (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - Keiper, Joseph, 1957, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 57)
  - Keith, Rit, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 58)
  - Kelban, Steven, undated (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - Keliher, Alice B., 1953 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Kelleher, Herbert, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Keller, Allan, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Keller, Joseph B., 1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Kellerman, Regina, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Kelley, Carmen Webster, 1952, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Kelley, Daniel M., 1960 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Kelley, Eugene J., 1959 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Kelley, Harry M., 1958, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Kellner, Jack, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Kelly, Christine, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Kelly, Helen, circa 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Kelly, Orrie R., undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Kelly, Patrick, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Kelly, Raymond, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Kelly, Walter, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Kemp, Edward L., 1964 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Kemp, Robert, undated (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Kempelman, Max, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Kemper, Becky, undated (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Kempin, Emily, undated (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Kendler, Howard H., 1952 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Keneally, undated (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1978 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Kennedy, Emma B., 1929 (Box 59, Folder 24, Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy, Eugene P., 1973 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy, Flo, undated (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Kennedy, John F., undated (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Kennedy, John F., Jr., 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Kennedy, John R., 1957, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Kennedy, John Stewart, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy, Stanislaus, undated (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Kennedy, Stephen P., 1959 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Kenneson, Thaddeus D., undated (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Kenny, Elizabeth, 1943 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Kent, Fred I., 1951 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Kent, James, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Kentera, Chris, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Keogh, Eugene, undated (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Keon, John, undated (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Keoppen, Arthur B., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Kerley, Robert F., undated (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Kern, Jerome, undated (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Kern, Jerome, undated (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Kerns, J. Alexander, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Kerrison, P.D., undated (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Kerry, Jonathan, undated (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Kettering, Charles Franklin, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Keusseff, Theodore, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Kevorkian, Hagop, undated (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Keyes, Joe, undated (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Khalil, undated (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Khuri, Nicola N., 1986 (Box 59, Folder 52)